https://alamo-trans.com/privacy-policy/

Home »
Privacy Policy
»
Privacy Policy
What Personally Identifiable Information is Collected
We do not collect personally identifiable information on our Site unless you voluntarily provide information about yourself via an electronic mail message or by filling out one of our online forms. By “personal information,” we mean data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, address or telephone number. For example, if you send us an email, we may use the information you provide to follow up via telephone or email. The information you provide will be kept confidential and will be used only to support your contact with Alamo.
How the Information You Provide is Used.
Should you send us your comments or questions via email to any email address provided on our Site, we will only share your communications with our employees capable of addressing your questions.
For your convenience, this Site may provide links to various web sites that we do not control. When you click on one of these links, you will be transferred out of our Site and connected to the web site of the organization or company that you selected. We are not responsible for the nature, quality or accuracy of the content or opinions expressed in such web sites, and such web sites are not investigated, monitored or checked for quality, accuracy or completeness by us.
TranslationEnglishEspañolFrançaisItalianoDeutsch Call Now! For a free quotecall us at:
210 692-1990
or Request a Quote online.
© 1991-2019 :: Alamo Transcription/HQ Secure Global Internet ::
all rights reserved
powered by Secure WordPress USA Hosting
Privacy Policy
